Wow.
This is a fantastic background.
I— I love this background.
But I have to change it.
My wife left me.
And I need a fresh start.
But how do I change wallpaper again?
Time to Google.
Okay, first result is an ad for
50% off divorce lawyers.
Very creepy.
But second result, here we go!
"Hi, just got back from Matrix Reloaded,"
"and now I wanna change the default background
to Neo beating up those guys."
"How do I change it?"
Ahem.
"Did you try to change the background?"
- "I also have this problem."
"That is all."
- "I don't have this problem
because I use a powermac!"
- "Har Har Har!"
"I didn't read the question?"
- "Does it work if you start in safe mode?"
- "Okay, I have your solution."
"Here's a photobucket link that will expire in 2004."
- "Hi, the link expired,
what was the solution?"
Tsk.
- "Why would you resurrect a solved thread?"
"I take my job as a moderator on a random"
"tech website no one has ever heard of very seriously!"
"Banned and thread locked!"
Okay, that was my fault,
I should have specified Windows 10.
Okay, here we go.
"Hi, my computer is starting
to smell like burnt wood."
"I think it's because I had
the same wallpaper for too long."
"How do I change it?"
"I don't have this problem because I use an iMac!"
- "Hello, it's me, friendly but not very helpful Indian."
"If you cannot change background,
consider updating your drivers."
"If that doesn't work, consider
buying a new graphics card."
"Good luck!"
"All izz well!"
- "Hello, I can actually teach you how to solve this."
"But beware, I am a software engineer,"
"and you are moving into a land
completely without visual help."
"Through a door to a dimension where
the end user's mind is a complete mystery."
"You are about to enter..."
"The Programmer Zone."
"The tutorial begins as any good tech tutorial should,"
"With entering your BIOS."
I have no idea what any of this means
Pretty sure that's Russian.
but Visual help, that's a great idea. Let's look for a video!
"Welcome to my tutorial on how to c-"
No this decade! thank you!
"what's up!!! if you want to change the desktop background image. This is the video, for you!"
Ugh, FINALLY!
"A lot of us have a computer"
"and on that computer we have an operating system"
"and that operating system-"
GET TO THE POINT
"-has a Desktop and that desktop has a background image."
"How do we change the image?"
Yes, how?
"That's a good question."
But first we talk about the history of the background.
*visible frustration* How long is this video!? ("*Unknown Tech Youtuber speech*")
*realization*
"- Linux Corporation..."
"And that's why,"
"Windows 8, while a bad operating system was the Ford Mustang of background providing!"
"So, how do we change background?-"
Okay, here we go.
"I will cover this in part two and much more!"
Yeah, I should have seen that one coming. I'm so tired of this!
I- I'm genuinely so desperate. I'm willing to click on Google page two
Background changing software,
but which one is the real one??!!???!?!? I...
*cries for help* I can't... I can't do it!
I could NEVER be a sniper!
uh.. If I could only ask someone but I'm not a member anywhere and calling tech support is too scary
I do have a reddit
ORIGINAL POST
"Hi, I've been trying to find how to change my background for two hours now"
"and I think, instead, I found God."
"Please help me!"
REPLIES
Guy 1: "Yes" Guy 2: "this..."
"as a chiropractor, I had the same problem"
"What worked for me is that I stopped using a gaming chair and switched to an office chair."
"without the carpal tunnel it was easy to change background."
"Hi..."
"Saw your question and I have a little something to add..."
"How DARE you!?"
"HOW DARE YOU!?!?"
"I have been providing tech support online since Windows 3,"
"and my eyes have never been this molested!"
"You dare to ask a tech question online,"
"Without providing your current Windows version,"
"your current brand of RAM,"
"and whether or not your computer has LED lights?!?!?!"
"I HATE you!"
"If I ever find, you death is too good!"
"I WOULD SURGICALLY REMOVE YOUR SPINE,"
"THEN PUT YOUR ENTIRE FAMILY THROUGH A MEAT GRINDER IN FRONT OF YOU"
"AND TURN THEM INTO TACOS!"
"TEX MEX TACOS"
"So you would spend the rest of your life in a hospital bed,"
"not only wondering why they had to die,"
"But also why their final existence would be an insult to the country of MEXICO!"
"Sorry, what I meant to say was; please provide more information so we can actually help you!"
Hey one more reply
"Kid,"
"It's nice that you found a higher power"
"Me? I work in tech support."
"All I know is hell."
This man is right.
I am asking for free help from the biggest victims in society...
Tech Support staff.
I should just follow that Mac guy's advice, and buy a new computer.
here! a brand new Windows 8!
But- it's... THE SAME!? Wh- Why!?
One Drive! what was that Indian's name?
*Gasp*
That's it- It's you!
It's always been you!!
it's not FAIR!!
IT'S. NOT. FAIR!!!
Searching for answers has led many to insanity. (Cries can be heard in the background)
We chase and trust they would be provided to us
But the search might just be theater for the power that be...
such is life in
"The Programmer Zone"